// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does SATA stand for?",
    answer: "Serial Advanced Technology Acquire",
    options: [
      "Super Advanced Technology Artificial",
      "Serial Advanced Technology Acquire",
      "Serial Automatic Team Advanced",
      "Serial Attack Technique Aviator"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is AGP?",
    answer: "Accelerated Graphic Port",
    options: [
      "Accelerated Graphic Port",
      "Accelerated Gaming Port",
      "Advanced Graphic Port",
      "Automatic Gaming Plane"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Lan Port is?",
    answer: "Allow a Computer To Connect a Network Using Wired Connection",
    options: [
      "Allow a Computer To Connect a Network Using Wired Connection",
      "To Watch Movie",
      "Allow to Advaned Unit",
      "Nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is a Hardware?",
    answer: "Any Part of Computer That has A Physical Structure",
    options: [
      "Use For Cooking",
      "Any Part of Computer That has A Physical Structure",
      "Just a Hard and Aware",
      "Nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is a Software?",
    answer: "Set of Instruction",
    options: [
      "Set of Instruction",
      "Set of Ideas",
      "Set of Language",
      "Set of Person"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Give 1 example of Hardware",
  answer: "Mouse",
   options: [
    "Mouse",
    "shield",
    "Pentelpen",
    "paper"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Give 1 Example of Software",
  answer: "MS-Word",
   options: [
    "MS-Word",
    "Pillow",
    "Liquid",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is CPU?",
  answer: "Central Processing Unit",
   options: [
    "Central Port Ultimate",
    "Central Pillar Unit",
    "Central Processor Unit",
    "Central Processing Unit"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 9,
  question: "What is PCI-E",
  answer: "Peripheral Component Interconnect Express",
   options: [
    "Peripheral Computing Int Entry",
    "Peripheral Component Interconnect Express",
    "Peripheral Casual Interconnect Eagle",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is RAM",
  answer: "Random Access Memory",
   options: [
    "Random Access Memory",
    "Read And Merit",
    "Read And Men",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 11,
  question: "What is LAN Stands for?",
  answer: "Local Area Network",
   options: [
    "Little Area Network",
    "Local Access Network",
    "Level Are Network",
    "Local Area Network"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 12,
  question: "What is MAN Stands for?",
  answer: "Metropolitan Area Network",
   options: [
    "Metropolitan Area Network",
    "Metropolitan Access Network",
    "Metropolitan Against Network",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 13,
  question: "What is WAN Stands for?",
  answer: "Wide Area Network",
   options: [
    "While Area Network",
    "Which Area Network",
    "Wide Area Network",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 14,
  question: "What is PAN Stands for?",
  answer: "Personal Area Network",
   options: [
    "Person Area Network",
    "Phase Area Network",
    "Port Area Network",
    "Personal Area Network"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 15,
  question: "Give 1 example of IP Address Class A",
  answer: "126.255.255.254",
   options: [
    "126.255.255.254",
    "192.168.1.1",
    "191.155.255.254",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 16,
  question: "What is TCP/IP Stands for?",
  answer: "Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol",
   options: [
    "Telecomunnication Control Panel/Internet Planner",
    "Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol",
    "Telepathy Control Protocal/Inteconnect Panel",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 17,
  question: "What is HTTP Stands for?",
  answer: "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol",
   options: [
    "Hyper Transfer Text Protocol",
    "Hyper Text Transfer Protocol",
    "Hyper Tips Transfer Protocol",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 18,
  question: "FTP stands for?",
  answer: "File Transfer Protocol",
   options: [
    "File Transfer Protocol",
    "Free Transfer Protocol",
    "Flex Text Protocol",
    "NOthing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 19,
  question: "RJ45 Stands for?",
  answer: "Registered Jack-45",
   options: [
    "Register Job-21",
    "Registered Joint-54",
    "Registered Jack-45",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 20,
  question: "USB Stands for?",
  answer: "Nothing",
   options: [
    "Ultra Super Bio",
    "Universal Serial Box",
    "Universal Set Bus",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
];
